Finding Aid for Enoch J. White papers, 1836-1877
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Enoch J. White papers 1836-1877
White, Enoch J., 1814-1878.
1 linear foot
86244 Aa 2
Lapeer, Michigan businessman; correspondence and other business papers.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Louis C. Cramton (donor no. 1677 ).
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Enoch J. White was a Lapeer, Michigan merchant, civil engineer, and banker.
The White collection includes correspondence and other business papers relating to his real estate transactions. There is also a personal account book and an account book of the White and Langdon general store, 1843-1845.
Subjects:
Banks and banking--Michigan--Lapeer.; Engineers--Michigan--Lapeer.; General stores--Michigan--Lapeer.; Lapeer (Mich.); Lapeer County (Mich.); Logging--Michigan--Lapeer County.; Lumbering--Michigan--Lapeer County.
- Correspondence
  - 1836-1837 (Box 1)
  - 1848-1850 (Box 1)
  - 1851-1855 (Box 1)
  - 1856-1860 (Box 1)
  - 1861-1865 (Box 1)
  - 1866-1867 (Box 1)
  - 1868-1870 (Box 1)
  - 1871-1877 and undated (Box 1)
- Other Materials
  - Income tax forms, 1862-1868 (Box 1)
  - Stock certificates, 1866-1867 (Box 1)
  - Business accounts and receipts, 7 folders (Box 1)
  - Sale agreement, 1868, of timber rights (Box 1)
  - Personal account book, 1870-1873 (Box 1)
  - Account book of White and Langdon general store, 1843-1845 (Box 1)